SOCIAL

- shailshah2526@gmail.com
- (+91) 9979906454
- in linkedin.com/in/shail-s
- github.com/Dil-Se-Developer

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages

- Javascript
- Typescript
- Python

Front-End

- HTML5
- CSS3
- React.js
- Redux
- React Testing
- UI Library

Back-End

- Node.js
- Express.js

Database

- MongoDB
- SQL

Tools

- VS Code
- Git

SOFT SKILLS

- Communication
- Teamwork
- Problem Solving
- Adaptability

LANGUAGES

- English
- Hindi
- Gujarati

Shail Shah



Software Developer

SUMMARY

Aiming to contribute to an organization that promotes my technical growth while aligning with its goals. With over 2 years of experience as a dedicated software developer, I bring a strong passion and expertise in software technologies.

EXPERIENCE

Arche Softronix Pvt. Ltd. | (Associate Front End Developer)

Sep 2022 - Present | Vadodara, India

PROACT

- In this healthcare project, I have experience with various packages including react-table, react-hook-form, react-select, react-zoom-pan-pinch, and several others.
- Developed a **Report Builder** module allowing users to generate dynamic reports based on their needs.
- Also developed modules, incorporated essential packages, and integrated APIs.

OPSACUITY

- Contributed to the ERP system by setting up the folder structure and configuring the routing architecture for different modules.
- I implemented comprehensive **Roles and Permissions** management and also utilized the **ApexCharts** package for graphs.
- I implemented **animations** in several parts of the module to make it more interactive and visually appealing for users.

SYNAPP

- In this healthcare project, I developed responsive modules and layouts with UI libraries like **Ant Design**, integrated essential packages, and connected APIs.
- I developed **utility** functions and **custom hooks** for common use throughout the project.

Arche Softronix Pvt. Ltd. | (Trainee Developer)

Mar 2022 - Aug 2022 | Vadodara, India

Money Mantra Financial Services | (Financial Services Associate)

May 2021 - Feb 2022 | Vadodara, India

Value Max Financial Services | (Financial Services Associate)

DEC 2020 - Apr 2021 | Vadodara, India

PERSONAL PROJECTS

1. Real Estate Website (7)

A project that has two roles: customer and agent. Customers can view property details, while agents can add, update, or delete listings.

React.js
Redux Toolkit
React Router
JSON Server

2. OLX Clone

EDUCATION

OLX UI clone with product adding, sorting, and filtering options, and a toggle dark theme.

React.js
Redux Toolkit
React Router
JSON Server
Axios

Online Courses

irses 2022

React - The Complete Guide (incl Hooks, React Router, Redux) - Maximilian Schwarzmüller

Axios

Online Courses

es 💮

HTML5,CSS3,JavaScript&Python

2020

Maharaja Sayajirao University, Vadodara B.Sc (Mathematics) (55%)

2020